A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.26 (A2000) FA470
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2000.063: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2000; AC.2000.063; 3.6 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3359, R3360, R3362.; 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3359, R3360, R3362.
  - Global Environment (GE), AC.2000.063.3
    - GE 9401 - NIMBKAR AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE (NARI) (INDIA) - LOW DENSITY BIOMASS GASIFICATION SYSTEM, 1993-1996 (Box R3362)
    - GE 9406 - DEUTSCHE GESELLSCHAFT FUR TECHNISCHE ZUSAMMENARBEIT (GTZ) (GERMANY) - SUBSTITUTE PLANT OILS FOR DIESEL FUEL, 1994-2000 (Box R3362)
    - GE 9503 - PRINCETON UNIVERSITY - STRATEGIC ASSESSMENT OF RENEWABLE ENERGY, 1994-1997 (Box R3362)
    - GE 9504 - CALIFORNIA STATE POLYTECHNIC UNIVERSITY - SOLAR-POWERED FREEZER SYSTEMS FOR ZIMBABWE AND THE REGION (POMONA), 1995-1996 (Box R3362)
    - GE 9601 - FREESA DEVELOPMENT FUND FOR SOUTH AFRICA - U.S. PROGRAM FOR SOUTH AFRICAN ENVIRONMENTALISTS, 1996 (Box R3362)
    - GE 9602 - SOLAR ENERGY RESEARCH AND EDUCATION FOUNDATION - CD-ROM ON SUSTAINABLE ENERGY AND ENVIRONMENTAL ISSUES, 1995-2000 (Box R3362)
    - GE 9605 - CLIMATE INSTITUTE - WASHINGTON SUMMIT ON PROTECTION OF THE WORLD'S CLIMATE, 1996-2000 (Box R3362)
    - GE 9609 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - BOOK, INTERNATIONAL PERSPECTIVES IN ENVIRONMENT, DEVELOPMENT AND HEALTH, 1995-2000 (Box R3362)
- AC.2000.064: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1979-2000; AC.2000.064; 7.2 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3361, R3363-R3367.; 6 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3361, R3363-R3367.
  - Health Sciences (HS), AC.2000.064.1
    - HS 9332 - BIOMASS USERS NETWORK, INC. (BUN) - HEALTH IMPACT OF EXPOSURE TO INDOOR AIR POLLUTION; IDENTIFY INTERVENTION STRATEGIES, 1992-1997 (Box R3361)
      Separated Materials
      Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
      - Biomass Version 12/13, 2000.064.001; 1 Item(s) Floppy disk: 3 1/2 inch
    - HS 9428 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - IMMUNOCHEMOTHERAPY FOR INDIAN VISCERAL LEISHMANIASIS, 1994-1997 (Box R3361)
    - HS 9429 - UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA - ARCHIVAL PROCESSING AND PRESERVATION OF KERR WHITE COLLECTION, 1993-1996 (Box R3361)
    - HS 9432 - AUSTRALIAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY - HEALTH TRANSITION CENTRE - HEALTH STATUS OF AGED IN INDIA, 1994-1997 (Box R3361)
    - HS 9442 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - CASE STUDY ON GLOBAL BURDEN OF DISEASE, 1992-1997 (Box R3361)
    - HS 9445 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - RESEARCH PRIORITIES FOR INTERVENTIONS IN ENVIRONMENT MEETING, 1994-1997 (Box R3361)
    - HS 9506 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - INSTITUTE OF MEDICINE - CORE DOCUMENTS ON CURRENT DYNAMICS IN GLOBAL HEALTH, 1994-1995 (Box R3361)
    - HS 9508 - UNIVERSITY OF YAOUNDE 1 (CAMEROON) - OPERATIONALIZING THE UNIT FOR HEALTH TECHNOLOGY, 1992-1997 (Box R3361)
    - HS 9511 - NEW ENGLAND MEDICAL CENTER HOSPITALS INC. - DIARRHEAL DISEASE, 1988-1998 (Box R3361)
    - HS 9513 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - MALARIA IMMUNIZATION OF PREGNANT WOMEN, 1994-1997 (Box R3361)
    - HS 9518 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - CHILD SURVIVAL CASE STUDY, 1994-1997 (Box R3361)
    - HS 9519 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - MEETING ON DISABLING SEQUELAE FOR GLOBAL BURDEN OF DISEASE, 1995-1997 (Box R3361)
    - HS 9524 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - MEETING ON THE ROLE CAPABILITY AND PERFORMANCE OF INTERNATIONAL ORGANIZATIONS FOR ADVANCING WORLD HEALTH, 1995-1997 (Box R3361)
    - HS 9527 - UNITED NATIONS CHILDREN'S FUND - EVALUATION OF TECHNICAL SUPPORT GROUPS INITIATIVE, 1995-1997 (Box R3361)
  - Population Sciences (PS), AC.2000.064.2
    - PS 9315 - EGYPTIAN FERTILITY CARE SOCIETY - NORPLANT ACCEPTABILITY STUDIES IN EGYPT, 1993-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3363)
    - PS 9435 - IKAMARI, LAWRENCE, 1990-1999 (Box R3363)
    - PS 9505 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - CHINESE COLLABORATION ON CLINICAL PHARMACOLOGY OF CONTRACEPTION, 1990-1997 (Box R3363)
    - PS 9508 - NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF CUYO (ARGENTINA) - EFFECTS OF GLYCOPROTEINS ON ACROSOME REACTION IN HUMAN SPERM, 1995-1996 (Box R3363)
    - PS 9509 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - CENTER FOR POPULATION AND FAMILY HEALTH - INTERNATIONAL REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH PROGRAM, 1995-1996 (Box R3363)
    - PS 9510 - MEXICAN INSTITUTE FOR FAMILY AND POPULATION RESEARCH (MEXICO) - ADOLESCENT SEXUALITY AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH IN MEXICO CITY, 1994-1997 (Box R3363)
    - PS 9519 - CARTER CENTER - GLOBAL DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVE, 1995-1998 (Box R3364)
    - PS 9520 - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH RESEARCH NETWORK IN FRANCOPHONE AFRICA (SENEGAL) - AFRICAN ATTENDANCE AT WORKSHOP ON REGIONAL RESEARCH AND FUNDING AGENDA, 1995-1997 (Box R3364)
    - PS 9621 - INTERNATIONAL ORGANIZATION FOR RESEARCH ON REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH (BRAZIL) - MARKET RESEARCH FOR UNIPLANT, 1995-1997 (Box R3364)
    - PS 9525 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - GUIDELINES FOR NON-LATEX CONDOMS, 1995-1997 (Box R3364)
    - PS 9602 - POPULATION COUNCIL - CHANGING SITUATION OF ADOLESCENTS IN EGYPT, 1995-1997 (Box R3364)
    - PS 9604 - WORLD CONGRESS ON HUMAN REPRODUCTION - APPLICATION OF MOLECULAR BIOLOGY TO CONTRACEPTIVE DEVELOPMENT AT THE IXth WORLD CONGRESS ON HUMAN REPRODUTION, 1995-1997 (Box R3364)
    - PS 9606 - KIDANE, ASMEROM - DEMOGRAPHIC CONSEQUENCES OF FAMINE IN ETHIOPIA, 1996-1997 (Box R3364)
    - PS 9613 - SCHERING RESEARCH FOUNDATION (GERMANY) - WORKSHOP ON POST-TESTICULAR SPERM MATURATION, 1996-1997 (Box R3364)
  - International Philanthropy (IP), AC.2000.064.3
    - IP 9503 - RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT FORUM FOR SCIENCE-LED DEVELOPMENT IN AFRICA (RANDFORUM) (KENYA) - ESTABLISH AFRICAN FOUNDATION FOR RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT (AFRAND), 1991-1997 (Box R3364)
  - International Security (IS), AC.2000.064.4
    - IS 9304 - UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA - NUCLEAR NONPROLIFERATION, 1993-1999 (Box R3364)
    - IS 9313 - MCGILL UNIVERSITY (CANADA) - "WHY NATIONS RENOUNCE NUCLEAR WEAPONS", 1992-1996 (Box R3364)
    - 94-8210-16 - STIMSON CENTER - CONFIDENCE-BUILDING MEASURES IN SOUTH ASIA, 1991-1997 (Box R3364)
    - IS 9422 - UNITED NATIONS ASSOCIATION OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA, INC. - SECURITY COUNCIL SUMMIT PROJECT, 1994-1999 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9502 - CARTER CENTER - INTERNATIONAL NEGOTIATION NETWORK MEETINGS, 1994-1997 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9506 - UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS (URBANA) - RESIDENCY FOR ARUN SINGH, 1995-1998 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9507 - NGO COMMITTEE ON DISARMAMENT INC - ACTIVITIES RELATED TO 1995 NON-PROLIFERATION TREATY CONFERENCE; PUBLISH DISARMAMENT TIMES, 1995-1999 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9515 - DEPAUL UNIVERSITY - MEETING ON ARMS CONTROL IN MIDDLE EAST, 1995-1996 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9519 - WISCONSIN PROJECT ON NUCLEAR ARMS CONTROL - "STOPPING WEAPONS OF MASS DESTRUCTION AT THE SOURCE", 1992-1996 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9520 - NAUTILUS OF AMERICA - INTERNET CONNECTION IN NORTH KOREA, 1995-1999 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9524 - UNDERDOG FILMS COOPERATIVE (NETHERLANDS)- FILM DOCUMENTARY: COURTING THE BOMB, 1995-1998 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9525 - UNION OF CONCERNED SCIENTISTS, INC. - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIP FOR TUSHAR RAVURI, 1995-1996 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9527 - (INTERNATIONAL SECURITY) - PROGRAM OPERATIONS - COOPERATION BETWEEN PAKISTAN AND INDIA, 1995-1997 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9530 - STOCKHOLM INTERNATIONAL PEACE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (SWEDEN) - PERSIAN GULF CONFERENCE PARTICIPATION BY PETER JONES, 1995-1997 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9532 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - AFRICA PROJECT ON CHEMICAL WEAPONS, 1995-1998 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9601 - CARNEGIE ENDOWMENT FOR INTERNATIONAL PEACE- SOUTH ASIAN PARTICIPATION IN 1996 MEETINGS ON NUCLEAR NONPROLIFERATION, 1995-1998 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9604 - (INTERNATIONAL SECURITY) - IMPACT OF CANBERRA COMMISSION ON THE ELIMINATION OF NUCLEAR WEAPONS, 1996 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9605 - ASIA SOCIETY - SYMPOSIUM ON SOUTH ASIA'S NUCLEAR FUTURE, 1996-1999 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9612 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR STRATEGIC STUDIES (ENGLAND) - INTERACTION WITH SCHOLARS FROM NORTH KOREA, 1996-1997 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9613 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - RECEPTIVITY TO ABOLITION IN AMERICAN NUCLEAR POLICY COMMUNITY, 1996-1997 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9616 - INTERNATIONAL PHYSICIANS FOR THE PREVENTION OF NUCLEAR WAR - NORTH ASIAN PARTICIPATION AT XII WORLD CONGRESS, 1995-1999 (Box R3365)
    - IS 9629 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - NUCLEAR ABOLITION AND U.S. MEDIA, 1996-1997 (Box R3365)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SI and SIE), AC.2000.064.5
    - SIE 9411 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR APPLIED SYSTEMS ANALYSIS (IIASA) (AUSTRIA) - INVOLVEMENT OF RESEARCHERS FROM DEVELOPING WORLD, 1994-1997 (Box R3365)
    - 94-8040-13 - POPULATION RESOURCE CENTER - CENSUS IN DEVELOPING PUBLIC POLICY, 1993-1996 (Box R3366)
    - 94-8040-25 - NATIONAL ORGANIZATION ON DISABILITY (NOD) - STUDENT INTERNSHIP PROGRAM, 1993-1996 (Box R3366)
    - 94-8040-25 - NATIONAL ORGANIZATION ON DISABILITY (NOD) - STUDENT INTERNSHIP PROGRAM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-1996 (Box R3366)
    - 94-8040-26 - ENVIRONMENT NOW - ENVIRONMENTAL RESTORATION AND PROTECTION, 1994-2000 (Box R3366)
    - SIE 9507 - 'TULANE UNIVERSITY-MULTI-CULTURALISM AND GENERAL SOCIAL SURVEY CONFERENCE, 1994-2000 (Box R3366)
    - SIE 9511 - WHITE HOUSE FELLOWS FOUNDATION - OUTREACH PROGRAM, 1994-1996 (Box R3366)
    - SI 9512 - FUTURE GENERATIONS - PENDEBA PROJECT IN TIBET, 1995-1997 (Box R3366)
    - SI 9514 - FOUNDATION FOR THE STUDY OF INDEPENDENT SOCIAL IDEAS - DISSENT MAGAZINE, 1995-1996 (Box R3366)
    - SIE 9515 - INTERNATIONAL CRIMINAL TRIBUNAL FOR THE FORMER YUGOSLAVIA (NETHERLANDS) - COMPUTER EQUIPMENT FOR YUGOSLAVIA AND RWANDA, 1995-1997 (Box R3366)
    - SI 9519 - COUNCIL ON FOREIGN RELATIONS - PROGRAM ON SOVEREIGNTY AND GOVERNANCE, 1994-1996 (Box R3366)
    - SI 9521 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - MARGARET SANGER PAPERS, 1995-1996 (Box R3366)
    - SI 9602 - SOUTHERN EDUCATION FOUNDATION, INC. ? PANEL ON EDUCATIONAL OPPORTUNITY AND POSTSECONDARY DESEGREGATION, 1995-1998 (Box R3366)
    - SI 9607 - WOMEN & FOUNDATIONS/CORPORATE PHILANTHROPY, 1979-2000; 4 folders. (Box R3367)
- AC.2000.073: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-2000; AC.2000.073; 1.2 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, Box R3370.; 1 standard record storage box, Box R3370.
  - African Initiatives (AI), AC.2000.073.1
    - AI 9212 - COUNCIL FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL RESEARCH IN AFRICA - ACADEMIC FREEDOM, 1990-1997 (Box R3370)
    - AI 9221 - SOCIAL SCIENCES RESEARCH COUNCIL - AFRICAN STUDIES IN THE UNITED STATES, 1987-1997 (Box R3370)
    - AI 9302 - UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN - EQUAL OPPORTUNITY RESEARCH PROJECT, 1993-2000 (Box R3370)
    - AI 9408 - GASAT ASSOCIATION (UNITED KINGDOM) - 8TH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON GENDER AND SCIENCE TECHNOLOGY, 1994-1996 (Box R3370)
    - AI 9504 - CATHOLIC RELIEF SERVICES - LOCAL DEVELOPMENT CAPACITY IN MOZAMBIQUE, 1995-2000 (Box R3370)
    - AI 9505 - FEMINIST PRESS -WOMEN'S STUDIES INTERNATIONAL PROGRAM AT THE 4TH U.N. WORLD CONFERENCE ON WOMEN IN BEIJING, 1995-2000 (Box R3370)
    - AI 9506 - INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL EDUCATION - LINKAGES IN HIGHER EDUCATION BETWEEN U.S. AND SOUTHERN AFRICAN UNIVERSITIES, 1995-1996 (Box R3370)
    - AI 9509 - COMMONWEALTH SECRETARIAT (ENGLAND) - CONFERENCE ON MATHEMATICS AS A BARRIER TO THE LEARNING OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY AMONG GIRLS IN INDIA, 1995-1997 (Box R3370)
    - AI 9510 - INTERNATIONAL COLLABORATIVE FOR SCIENCE EDUCATION AND THE ENVIRONMENT, INC. - WOMEN'S GROUP IN ZANZIBAR TO ORGANIZE SCIENCE AND ENVIRONMENTAL PROGRAMS, 1995-2000 (Box R3370)
    - AI 9514 - WORLD LEARNING - GLOBAL PARTNERSHIP FOR NGO STUDIES, EDUCATION AND TRAINING, 1995-1996 (Box R3370)
    - AI 9515 - OPERATION CROSSROADS AFRICA - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1995-2000 (Box R3370)
    - AI 9516 - UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA - HOUSEHOLD PERSPECTIVE TO AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT, 1995-1997 (Box R3370)
    - AI 9517 - NEW YORK ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - MERIT REVIEW AND SELECTION FOR AFRICA HIGHER EDUCATION AND SCIENTIFIC RESEARCH, 1995-2000 (Box R3370)
- AC.2000.076: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1992-1999; AC.2000.076; 2.4 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3371-R3372.; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3371-R3372.
  - African Initiatives (AI), AC.2000.076.1
    - AI 9518 - NATIONAL URBAN RECONSTRUCTION AND HOUSING AGENCY (SOUTH AFRICA) - EXPERIMENTAL RENTAL HOUSING IN SOUTH AFRICA, 1995-1998 (Box R3371)
    - AI 9603 - ASSOCIATION FOR WOMEN IN DEVELOPMENT - SEVENTH INTERNATIONAL FORUM "BEYOND BEIJING: FROM WORDS TO ACTION", 1996 (Box R3371)
    - AI 9604 - ORGANIZATION OF AFRICAN UNITY (ETHIOPIA) - EMPOWERMENT OF WOMEN CONFERENCE, 1996 (Box R3371)
  - School Reform (SR), AC.2000.076.2
    - SR 9402 - PITON FOUNDATION - CENTER FOR QUALITY SCHOOLS - TRAINING OF THE COLLABORATIVE DECISION-MAKING COMMITTEES, 1993-1996 (Box R3371)
    - SR 9502 - BROWN UNIVERSITY - DESIGN AND DEVELOPMENT WORKING PARTY, 1992-1999 (Box R3371)
    - SR 9502 - BROWN UNIVERSITY - DESIGN AND DEVELOPMENT WORKING PARTY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1992-1999; 2 folders. (Box R3371)
    - SR 9506 - PUBLIC AGENDA FOUNDATION - TEACHERS ATTITUDES REGARDING EDUCATION REFORM SURVEY, 1992-1996 (Box R3372)
    - SR 9509 - KNOWLEDGE NETWORK FOR ALL AMERICA'S CHILDREN - CITIZEN'S HANDBOOK ON SCHOOL REFORM, 1995-1997 (Box R3372)
    - SR 9510 - FIELDING INSTITUTE - "MANAGING CHANGE IN THE PUBLIC SECTOR" ROUND TABLE, 1995-1996 (Box R3372)
    - SR 9601 - COUNCIL ON FOUNDATIONS - GRANTMAKERS FOR EDUCATION PROJECT, 1995-1997 (Box R3372)
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2000.076.3
    - AH 9504 - MUSEUMS UNIVERSALLY SUPPORTING EDUCATION AND ENTERTAINMENT (MUSEE) - BC CONFERENCE: INTEGRATING GLOBAL KNOWLEDGE IN ART AND CULTURE, 1994-1996 (Box R3372)
    - AH 9535 - NETWORK OF LATIN AMERICAN PRODUCERS OF INDEPENDENT CONTEMPORARY ART (BRAZIL) - BC CONFERENCE: PLURAL, MULTIPLE AND DIVERSE IN CONTEMPORARY ART PRODUCTION, 1994-1996 (Box R3372)
  - Arts and Sciences (AS), AC.2000.076.4
    - AS 9310 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - BC CONFERENCE: BIOTECHNOLOGY FOR INTEGRATED PEST MANAGEMENT, 1992-1997 (Box R3372)
  - International Philanthropy (IP), AC.2000.076.5
    - IP 9502 - PUERTO RICO COMMUNITY FOUNDATION - BC CONFERENCE: PHILANTHROPY AND DEVELOPMENT, 1994-1996 (Box R3372)
- AC.2000.091: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-2004; AC.2000.091; 7.2 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3373-R3378.; 6 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3373-R3378.
  - Fellowships (F), AC.2000.091.1
    - F-PS GHANA - AHIADEKE, CLEMENT, 1987-1996 (Box R3373)
    - F-AS MOZAMBIQUE - ALCANTARA SANTOS, LUISA MARIA KINGWELL, 1991-1996 (Box R3373)
    - F-AS PHILIPPINES - ALDEMITA, RHODORA, 1990-1996 (Box R3373)
    - F-AS INDIA - BABU, RANGANATHAN CHANDRA, 1994-1996; 2004 (Box R3373)
    - F-AS COLOMBIA - CALDERON-URREA, A., 1990-1996 (Box R3373)
    - F-AS BRAZIL - CARVALHO, LUIS JOAQUIM CASTELO, 1993-1996 (Box R3373)
    - F-PS INDIA - CHAKRABORTY, I., 1992-1995 (Box R3373)
    - F-AS USA - CHAMPOUX, MICHAEL C., 1990-1996 (Box R3373)
    - F-PS MALAYSIA/USA - CHAN, ANGELIQUE, 1992-1995 (Box R3373)
    - F-AS INDIA - CHAUDHURY, ASHOK, 1994-1995 (Box R3373)
    - F-AS CHINA - CHEN XIONGFONG, 1992-1995 (Box R3373)
    - F-AS CHINA - CHENG XIONGYING, 1993-1997 (Box R3373)
    - F-AS THAILAND - CHUNWONGSE JULAPARK, 1989-1995 (Box R3374)
    - F-AS CHINA - DENG WANYIN, 1989-1996 (Box R3374)
    - F-PS INDIA - DHARMALINGAM, ARUNACHALAM, 1990-1995 (Box R3374)
    - F-PS INDIA - DHIR, RAVINDA NATH, 1991-1994 (Box R3374)
    - F-AS PHILIPPINES - EBORA, REYNALDO V., 1990-1995 (Box R3374)
    - F-PS NIGERIA - FAPOHUNDA, BOLAJI, 1989-1995 (Box R3374)
    - F-AS NIGERIA - FATOKUN, CHRISTIAN ADEMOLA, 1990-1992 (Box R3374)
    - F-PS CHINA - GAO HUI-BAO, 1992-1997 (Box R3374)
    - F-PS CHINA - GUO SHU-YING, 1992-1996 (Box R3374)
    - F-AS CHINA - HU TIANHUA, 1989-1995 (Box R3374)
    - F-AS INDIA - IBRAHIM, SYED MOSHIN, 1991-1995 (Box R3374)
    - F-PS INDIA - ISHWAD, PALLAVI C., 1992-1995 (Box R3375)
    - F-AS INDIA - JAIN, RAJINDER KUMAR, 1991-1996 (Box R3375)
    - F-AS INDIA - JAISHREE, CHITTOOR M., 1990-1997 (Box R3375)
    - F-AS UGANDA - KABEERE, FLAVIA, 1989-1996 (Box R3375)
    - F-AS PAKISTAN - KARIM, SHAHID, 1994-1996 (Box R3375)
    - F-PS INDIA - KAUSHIC, CHARU, 1992-1995 (Box R3375)
    - F-AS KENYA - KINUTHIA, MARGARET, 1991-1996 (Box R3375)
    - F-AS IVORY COAST - KONAN, KOFFI N'DA, 1994-1996 (Box R3375)
    - F-PS INDIA - KUMAR, G. PRADEEP, 1991-1997 (Box R3375)
    - F-PS IVORY COAST - KOUAME, AKA, 1992-1995 (Box R3375)
    - F-PS INDIA - LALORAYA, MALINI, 1992-1997 (Box R3375)
    - F-PS PANAMA - LASSO DEL CASTILLO, JAIME LEONEL, 1991-1994 (Box R3375)
    - F-PS CHINA - LEI HANQIN, 1992-1996 (Box R3375)
    - F-AS CHINA - LI DADONG, 1990-1998 (Box R3376)
    - F-AS CHINA - LI ZHONGYI, 1989-1995 (Box R3376)
    - F-AS PAKISTAN - MAKHDOOM, RAHAT, 1994-1996 (Box R3376)
    - F-PS USA - MATERNOWSKA, MARY C., 1991-1996 (Box R3376)
    - F-AS PHILIPPINES - MENANCIO-HAUTEA, D., 1990-1993 (Box R3376)
    - F-AS UGANDA - MIJUMBI, PETER B., 1990-1999 (Box R3376)
    - F-PS INDIA - MITRA, JAYASHREE, 1992-1995 (Box R3376)
    - F-AS INDIA - MUKHOPADHYAY, KUNAL, 1992-1997 (Box R3376)
    - F-AS VIETNAM - NGUYEN DUC THANH, 1995-1996 (Box R3376)
    - F-AS MALAWI - NGWIRA, PATRICIA, 1990-1997 (Box R3376)
    - F-PS NIGERIA - OGWUEGBU, STEPHEN O., 1992-1995 (Box R3376)
    - F-PS NIGERIA - OKANLAWAN, ABAYOMI, 1991-1995 (Box R3376)
    - F-AS KENYA - OMAMO, STEVEN WERE, 1989-1995 (Box R3376)
    - F-PS NIGERIA - OSIRIKE, ANIMAM BEECROFT, 1987-1995 (Box R3376)
    - F-PS SUDAN - OSMAN, EL-RAYAH A.A., 1992-1995 (Box R3376)
    - F-PS USA - PARKER, SUSAN WENDY, 1992-1996 (Box R3377)
    - F-PS INDIA - PHILIP, GUNDALA HAROLD, 1991-1997 (Box R3377)
    - F-AS INDIA - POTNIS, AARDRA ARUN, 1992-1996 (Box R3377)
    - F-PS INDIA - RAM, FAUJDAR, 1992-1995 (Box R3377)
    - F-AS INDIA - RAO, GUNDIMEDA JWALA NARASIMHA, 1992-1995 (Box R3377)
    - F-AS PHILIPPINES - REDONA, EDILBERTO D., 1990-1997 (Box R3377)
    - F-AS PHILIPPINES - ROMERO, GABRIEL ORTEGA, 1989-1996 (Box R3377)
    - F-PS NEPAL - SHRESTHA, DEVENDRA PRASAD, 1992-1996 (Box R3377)
    - F-AS MALAWI - SIBALE, ELIZABETH MARY, 1990-1996 (Box R3377)
    - F-AS INDIA - SINDHU, ANOOP SINGH, 1992-1997 (Box R3377)
    - F-AS CHINA - SONG WENYUAN, 1992-1996 (Box R3377)
    - F-AS UGANDA - SSEMWANGA, JAMES R. K., 1992-1998 (Box R3378)
    - F-AS CHINA - SU JIN, 1993-1998 (Box R3378)
    - P-AS PHILIPPINES - TABIEN, RODANTE E., 1990-1997 (Box R3378)
    - F-AS CHINA - TANG KEXUAN, 1989-1996 (Box R3378)
    - F-PS VIETNAM - THANG, NGUYEN MINH, 1992-1996 (Box R3378)
    - F-AS INDIA - UMARANI, KAMASANI, 1992-1998 (Box R3378)
    - F-PS ARGENTINA - VISCONTI, PABLO E., 1992-1995 (Box R3378)
    - F-AS CHINA - WANG HONG, 1989-1996 (Box R3378)
    - RF 90032 A 81 - WICHITRA, JUTIDAMRONGPHAN, 1991-1997 (Box R3378)
    - F-PS USA - WOLFF, ROBERT BRENT K., 1991-1996 (Box R3378)
    - F-AS-CHINA - XIAO JINUA, 1989-1999 (Box R3378)